<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAN on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/san/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SAN on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 16:24:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/san/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Cloud: Hardware Consider* **Path 1: Reuse Existing Hardware.** If your current servers and storage ran VMware vSphere reliably, you might prefer to repurpose them for the new solution. This path favors a platform that is **flexible with hardware compatibility**. Microsoft&#39;s traditional Windows Server &#43; Hyper-V is very accommodating here – it can run on a wide range of commodity servers and supports classic external SAN storage for clusters. In fact, Windows Server 2025 (with Hyper-V and Failover Clustering) offers much greater flexibility to **leverage existing gear** than Azure Local does. If your goal is to **maximize use of existing hardware**, the Windows Server route is often the best choice. It allows clustering with either shared storage (e.g., an iSCSI/FC SAN or NAS) or with internal disks via Storage Spaces Direct – giving you options to integrate with whatever infrastructure you already have.tions - Part III</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/beyond-cloud-hardware-considerations-part-iii/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 12:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/beyond-cloud-hardware-considerations-part-iii/</guid>
      <description>Hardware Considerations: Build Your Cloud on Your Terms Series Recap: In Part 1 of this series, we examined the total cost of ownership (TCO) implications of different post-VMware paths, comparing capital expenditure vs. subscription models across on-premises Hyper-V, Azure Local (formerly Azure Stack HCI), and Azure VMware Solution (AVS). In Part 2, we dove into licensing – analyzing how VMware vSphere licensing stacks up against Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s offerings (Windows Server and Azure Local) in 2025, and what those licensing differences mean for choosing a virtualization platform.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
