<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows Server on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/windows-server/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows Server on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 17:35:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/windows-server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Cloud: What&#39;s Next for Microsoft On-Prem - Part IX</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/beyond-cloud-whats-next-microsoft-on-prem-part-ix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/beyond-cloud-whats-next-microsoft-on-prem-part-ix/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon This blog post is part of the &amp;ldquo;Beyond the Cloud: The Case for On-Premises Virtualization&amp;rdquo; series and will cover:&#xA;Windows Server Roadmap: Upcoming features and long-term vision Azure Local Evolution: Next-generation capabilities and integration Hybrid Strategy: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s direction for on-premises and cloud integration Container Integration: Kubernetes and container platform roadmap AI and ML Integration: Edge AI capabilities in future releases Security Enhancements: Zero trust and advanced security features Management Tools: Future of System Center and Azure management Investment Guidance: Planning for long-term technology adoption Series Navigation Introduction: Beyond the Cloud: Rethinking Virtualization Post-VMware Part I: Beyond the Cloud: CapEx vs Subscription TCO Analysis Part II: Beyond the Cloud: 2025 Virtualization Licensing Guide Part III: Beyond the Cloud: Hardware Considerations Part IV: Beyond the Cloud: Feature Face-Off Part V: Beyond the Cloud: Arc Enable Everything Part VI: Beyond the Cloud: Disconnected &amp;amp; Rugged Part VII: Beyond the Cloud: ESXi to Hyper-V in 30 Days Part VIII: Beyond the Cloud: Three Paths Off VMware Part IX: What&amp;rsquo;s Next for Microsoft On-Prem - Windows Server &amp;amp; Azure Local (This Post - Coming Soon) This post is currently in development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful, Practical, Proven: Why WSFC and Hyper‑V Deserve a Second Look</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2025-06-06-powerful-practical-proven-why-wsfc-and-hyperv-deserve-a-second-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2025-06-06-powerful-practical-proven-why-wsfc-and-hyperv-deserve-a-second-look/</guid>
      <description>Why Choose Windows Server Failover Clustering (WSFC) with Hyper‑V Over VMware Virtualization is a cornerstone of modern IT infrastructure, and VMware vSphere has long been a leader in this space. However, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows Server Failover Clustering (WSFC) with Hyper‑V offers a compelling alternative for organizations seeking a cost-effective, high-performance virtualization platform. In this post, targeted at IT professionals, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore why WSFC with Hyper‑V is a strong alternative to VMware – emphasizing the ability to leverage existing hardware (reducing new hardware costs), the performance benefits of Hyper‑V, available management tools, feature comparisons with VMware, and a look at licensing and cost differences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows Terminal on Windows Servers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-01-31-enable-windows-terminal-on-windows-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 15:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-01-31-enable-windows-terminal-on-windows-servers/</guid>
      <description>Early this year I had written a blog talking about how to enable Windows Terminal on Windows Server. However, I deleted that blog and all content and can&amp;rsquo;t find my backups so I am re-writing it once again. I wanted to share my experience with installing Windows Terminal on Windows Server and what I had to do to get around the blockers I ran into. As I mentioned in the last blog I had ran into issues that other bloggers never seemed to run into when installing Windows Terminal.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
