<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VMware on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/vmware/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VMware on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:58:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/vmware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CapEx vs Subscription: TCO Modeling for Hyper-V &amp; Azure Local &amp; AVS</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/capex-subscription-tco-modeling-hyper-azure-local-avs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/capex-subscription-tco-modeling-hyper-azure-local-avs/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In our previous blog post, we explored why organizations are reconsidering their virtualization strategy post-VMware and highlighted the often-overlooked value of Windows Server Failover Clustering with Hyper-V. Now, in this first follow-up post of the &amp;quot;Beyond the Cloud: The Case for On-Premises Virtualization&amp;quot; series, we dive into the financial side of that decision. Specifically, we will compare the five-year Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) for three possible platforms to run a 100-Virtual Machine (VM) workload:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful, Practical, Proven: Why WSFC and Hyper‑V Deserve a Second Look</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2025-06-06-powerful-practical-proven-why-wsfc-and-hyperv-deserve-a-second-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2025-06-06-powerful-practical-proven-why-wsfc-and-hyperv-deserve-a-second-look/</guid>
      <description>Why Choose Windows Server Failover Clustering (WSFC) with Hyper‑V Over VMware Virtualization is a cornerstone of modern IT infrastructure, and VMware vSphere has long been a leader in this space. However, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows Server Failover Clustering (WSFC) with Hyper‑V offers a compelling alternative for organizations seeking a cost-effective, high-performance virtualization platform. In this post, targeted at IT professionals, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore why WSFC with Hyper‑V is a strong alternative to VMware – emphasizing the ability to leverage existing hardware (reducing new hardware costs), the performance benefits of Hyper‑V, available management tools, feature comparisons with VMware, and a look at licensing and cost differences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Virtualization Post-VMware</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/rethinking-virtualization-post-vmware/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 19:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/rethinking-virtualization-post-vmware/</guid>
      <description>From My Perspective as a Microsoft Azure Hybrid MVP – Two Decades in Microsoft Hybrid &amp;amp; HCI I write this blog as a longtime Microsoft advocate with two decades of hands-on experience—from early Hyper-V in 2008 to today&amp;rsquo;s Azure Local. This series aims to highlight the potential of Windows Server Failover Clustering (WSFC) as a viable alternative for organizations transitioning away from VMware, especially in light of Broadcom&amp;rsquo;s acquisition. While I value Azure&amp;rsquo;s Cloud and Hybrid offerings, I believe Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s current messaging overlooks WSFC&amp;rsquo;s capabilities in providing cost-effective, high-availability solutions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
