<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TCO on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/tco/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TCO on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/tco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Real Cost of Virtualization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/real-cost-virtualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 13:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/real-cost-virtualization/</guid>
      <description>The invoice arrived, and the meeting quickly followed.&#xA;For nearly two decades, the &amp;ldquo;cost of virtualization&amp;rdquo; was a line item we grumbled about but accepted. It was the &amp;ldquo;VMware Tax,&amp;rdquo; the price of admission for a stable, feature-rich datacenter. But in the wake of the Broadcom acquisition and the subsequent licensing overhaul, that tax has, for many organizations, turned into a ransom.&#xA;This isn&amp;rsquo;t just about price hikes. It&amp;rsquo;s about a fundamental shift in how infrastructure is consumed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Hyper-V Renaissance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hyper-renaissance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hyper-renaissance/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A Perfect Storm Creates Opportunity If you&amp;rsquo;ve been watching the virtualization market over the past eighteen months, you&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed something extraordinary: a once-stable industry thrown into chaos by a single acquisition. When Broadcom completed its $69 billion purchase of VMware in November 2023, few anticipated how dramatically—and rapidly—the landscape would shift. What followed wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a pricing adjustment; it was a fundamental restructuring that has sent shockwaves through data centers worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Cloud: 2025 Virtualization Licensing Guide - Part II</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/choosing-your-virtualization-platform-2025-licensing-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/choosing-your-virtualization-platform-2025-licensing-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Part 2 of our &amp;ldquo;Beyond the Cloud: The Case for On-Premises Virtualization&amp;rdquo; series. In our introductory post, we explored why organizations are reconsidering their virtualization strategies post-VMware acquisition. In Part 1, we conducted a detailed five-year Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) analysis comparing Windows Hyper-V, Azure VMware Solution (AVS), and Azure Local, revealing how different cost structures impact long-term budgets.&#xA;A key factor driving those cost differences was how each platform&amp;rsquo;s licensing model works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Cloud: CapEx vs Subscription TCO Analysis - Part I</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/capex-subscription-tco-modeling-hyper-azure-local-avs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/capex-subscription-tco-modeling-hyper-azure-local-avs/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In our previous blog post, we explored why organizations are reconsidering their virtualization strategy post-VMware and highlighted the often-overlooked value of Windows Server Failover Clustering with Hyper-V. Now, in this first follow-up post of the &amp;quot;Beyond the Cloud: The Case for On-Premises Virtualization&amp;quot; series, we dive into the financial side of that decision. Specifically, we will compare the five-year Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) for three possible platforms to run a 100-Virtual Machine (VM) workload:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
