<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Arc on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Arc on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:23:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure Stack HCI - Part IX - Azure Kubernetes Service Deployment</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/azure-stack-hci-part-ix-azure-kubernetes-service-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/azure-stack-hci-part-ix-azure-kubernetes-service-deployment/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I plan to blog about everything I know about Azure Stack HCI. So, it should be a very short blog series. Just kidding. Again, I tend to blog about subjects that I am currently working on or will be currently working on. So, Azure Stack HCI is fresh on my mind again these days.
I now have Azure Stack HCI cluster deployed. We can manage it using Windows Admin Center or PowerShell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas!</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas/</guid>
      <description>For those that are not aware there is a very awesome resource provided by the Cloud Family called the Festive Tech Calendar. The Festive Tech Calendar is a free, month-long, fun tech event that takes place throughout December. The event features new content from different communities and people around the globe. The event is organized by Cloud Family and is aimed at people from all communities who want to participate in a fun and engaging session that is a bit different from a normal conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My MicroK8s Cluster Is Now Manged by Azure. What is next? - Part II - Monitoring</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure-part-ii-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure-part-ii-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>This is next blog in a series of blogs I just started that share my experiences with integrating Azure services with my on-premises deployment of MicroK8s Kubernetes cluster running in WSL. These blog series are an extension of another blog series I did called MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc.
At a high level there is a lot of Azure Services we can integrate and use with our Kubernetes clusters running anywhere, such as on-premises, or even GCP and AWS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My MicroK8s Cluster Is Now Manged by Azure. What is next?</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure/</guid>
      <description>In a previous blog series MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc - A blog series about my experiences with MicroK8S, WSL, and Azure Arc I had a curiosity to see if I could deploy MicroK8s on my WIndows 10 WSL instance and then manage the WSL instance with Azure Arc and then manage the MicroK8s cluster using Arc-enabled Kubernetes.
So let&amp;rsquo;s refresh here a little. I was able to get a MicroK8s cluster deployed on WSL running on my Windows 10 laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc -Part IV - Arc Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-iv-arc-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-iv-arc-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I am going to discuss my experiences with MicroK8S, installing it on Windows Subsystem for Linux, and how to connect the cluster to Azure using Azure Arc-Enabled Kubernetes.
The blog will be broken up into the following three sections:
Installing MicroK8s on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) Azure Arc-enabled servers: Installing Azure Connected Machine Agent Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes: Connecting my MicroK8S cluster to Azure Managing MicroK8s Cluster with Azure Arc-Enabled Kubernetes In this blog I will discuss my experience connecting my newly deploy MicroK8s cluster to Azure using Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc -Part III - Azure Arc</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-iii-azure-arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-iii-azure-arc/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I am going to discuss my experiences with MicroK8S, installing it on Windows Subsystem for Linux, and how to connect the cluster to Azure using Azure Arc-Enabled Kubernetes.
The blog will be broken up into the following three sections:
Installing MicroK8s on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) Azure Arc-enabled servers: Installing Azure Connected Machine Agent Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes: Connecting my MicroK8S cluster to Azure Azure Arc-Enabled Servers - Installing the Azure Connected Machine Agent (Azure Arc Agent) In this blog I will discuss my experience installing the Azure Arc agent, also known as the Azure Connected Machine Agent in in order to manage this WSL instance within Azure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc - Part II - Installing MicroK8S on WSL</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-ii-installing-microk8s-wsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-ii-installing-microk8s-wsl/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I am going to discuss my experiences with MicroK8S, installing it on Windows Subsystem for Linux, and how to connect the cluster to Azure using Azure Arc-Enabled Kubernetes.
The blog will be broken up into the following three sections:
Installing MicroK8s on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) Azure Arc-enabled servers: Installing Azure Connected Machine Agent Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes: Connecting my MicroK8S cluster to Azure Installing MicroK8s on WSL In this blog I will discuss my experience with installing Microk8s on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc/</guid>
      <description>I recently started a new job with a company that isn&amp;rsquo;t a 100% Microsoft shop. It has been many years since I have worked in a environment that everyone wasn&amp;rsquo;t drinking the Microsoft Kool-Aid. Not a bad thing if you do, I did and I loved that flavor. However, new job means new challenges and new way of doing things.
In this blog series I am going to discuss my experiences with MicroK8S.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
