<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Arc on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Arc on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:47:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Eight Custom Locations</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-custom-locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-custom-locations/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 8 - Eight Custom Locations On the eighth day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure carved for me: Eight Custom Locations, sculpting new possibilities for service migrations and innovations.
Day 8: Expanding Horizons with Azure Arc Custom Locations Azure Arc brings us eight maids a-milking, each nurturing the growth of Azure services in the fertile fields of our own environments, no matter how unique or specific they may be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Seven Policies Ringing</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-policies-ringing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 15:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-policies-ringing/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 7 - Seven Policies Ringing On the seventh day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure secured me: Seven Policies Ringing, ensuring governance across clouds with precision and clarity.
Day 7: Securing Multicloud Governance with Azure Arc Azure Arc brings to us seven swans a-swimming, gracefully navigating the waters of multicloud governance, representing the beauty and elegance of a well-orchestrated security strategy.
Harnessing the Power of Policy-Driven Management: Azure Policy: Extend governance across Azure and non-Azure environments, applying consistent policies everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Six Apps Deploying</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-apps-deploying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 19:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-apps-deploying/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 6 - Six Apps Deploying On the sixth day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure showed to me: Six Apps Deploying, marking innovation at its finest for productivity employing.
Day 6: Fostering Innovation with Azure Arc Azure Arc brings six geese a-laying, each laying the foundation for innovative app deployment, orchestrating the birth of new solutions with cloud-native development across any environment.
Powering Agile Application Development: End-to-End Solutions: From local data collection to cloud-based analytics, Azure Arc provides a comprehensive platform for app development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Five Golden Savings</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-golden-savings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 19:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-golden-savings/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 5 - Five Golden Savings On the fifth day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure saved for me: Five Golden Savings, bringing hybrid benefits that make fiscal sense truly engraving.
The Fifth Day of Arc-mas: Embracing Azure Arc&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Five Golden Savings&amp;rdquo; Azure Hybrid Benefit: A Beacon of Cost Optimization Azure Arc&amp;rsquo;s Hybrid Benefit transforms existing Windows Server and SQL Server licenses with Software Assurance or qualifying subscription licenses into a cost-saving strategy within Azure Arc-enabled services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Four Nodes Connecting</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-nodes-connecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 19:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-nodes-connecting/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 4 - Four Nodes Connecting On the fourth day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure offered me: Four Nodes Connecting, bringing together a variety of choices for infrastructure selecting.
Day 4: Flexible Infrastructure and Connectivity Azure Arc&amp;rsquo;s fourth gift to us is the power of connection — linking diverse infrastructures from the conventional to the cutting-edge, and ensuring that whether it&amp;rsquo;s Windows Server, Linux, VMware vSphere, or Azure Stack HCI, your nodes are all part of the same, seamlessly managed ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Three Services Scaling</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-services-scaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 19:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-services-scaling/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 3 - Three Services Scaling On the third day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure gifted me: Three Services Scaling, with Azure SQL and PostgreSQL providing no downtime feeling.
Day 3: Data Insights - Azure Arc for Data Services Azure Arc celebrates the season by bringing the robustness of Azure data services directly to Kubernetes clusters, regardless of their location. Imagine Azure SQL Managed Instance and Azure Database for PostgreSQL, not just housed within Azure but anywhere you require – without missing a beat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Two Clusters Flexing</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-clusters-flexing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-clusters-flexing/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 2 - Two Cluster Flexing On the second day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure sent to me: Two Clusters Flexing, managed from Azure, yet running so free.
Embracing Duality: Kubernetes Clusters and Azure Data Services Azure Arc brings duality and harmony between Kubernetes clusters and Azure data services, offering a seamless operational experience that&amp;rsquo;s both managed from Azure and capable of running anywhere.
Azure Arc&amp;rsquo;s Key Messages: Consistent Development and Operations: Azure Arc fosters uniform development and operations of cloud-native applications across any Kubernetes environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure ArcMas - A Console In A Cloud Tree</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-console-cloud-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-console-cloud-tree/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 1 - Centralized Management On the first day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure granted me: A Console in a Cloud Tree.
Single Control Plane Across Environments Azure Arc is like the partridge in a pear tree at the heart of your environment&amp;rsquo;s management, extending the familiar Azure services to wherever your resources reside. It simplifies the complex, multi-faceted nature of modern IT landscapes by offering a unified management experience, enabling you to view and manage your resources irrespective of their physical or cloud location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure ArcMas - Introduction</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 22:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introducing The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: A Festive Journey Through Cloud Management Happy Holidays, tech enthusiasts! 🎄 As we count down to the end of the year, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to bring you a special gift: &amp;ldquo;The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas.&amp;rdquo; This series is inspired by the classic carol &amp;ldquo;The Twelve Days of Christmas,&amp;rdquo; with a tech twist that celebrates the gifts Azure Arc delivers to IT professionals each day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-12-13-the-12-days-of-azure-arc-mas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 21:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-12-13-the-12-days-of-azure-arc-mas/</guid>
      <description>The The Festive Tech Calendar is a free, month-long, fun tech event that takes place throughout December. The event features new content from different communities and people around the globe. The event is organized by Cloud Family and is aimed at people from all communities who want to participate in a fun and engaging session that is a bit different from a normal conference. On the 6th of December I did a session called &amp;ldquo;The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Stack HCI - Part IX - Azure Kubernetes Service Deployment</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/azure-stack-hci-part-ix-azure-kubernetes-service-deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/azure-stack-hci-part-ix-azure-kubernetes-service-deployment/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I plan to blog about everything I know about Azure Stack HCI. So, it should be a very short blog series. Just kidding. Again, I tend to blog about subjects that I am currently working on or will be currently working on. So, Azure Stack HCI is fresh on my mind again these days.
I now have Azure Stack HCI cluster deployed. We can manage it using Windows Admin Center or PowerShell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas!</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas/</guid>
      <description>For those that are not aware there is a very awesome resource provided by the Cloud Family called the Festive Tech Calendar. The Festive Tech Calendar is a free, month-long, fun tech event that takes place throughout December. The event features new content from different communities and people around the globe. The event is organized by Cloud Family and is aimed at people from all communities who want to participate in a fun and engaging session that is a bit different from a normal conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My MicroK8s Cluster Is Now Manged by Azure. What is next? - Part II - Monitoring</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure-part-ii-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure-part-ii-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>This is next blog in a series of blogs I just started that share my experiences with integrating Azure services with my on-premises deployment of MicroK8s Kubernetes cluster running in WSL. These blog series are an extension of another blog series I did called MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc.
At a high level there is a lot of Azure Services we can integrate and use with our Kubernetes clusters running anywhere, such as on-premises, or even GCP and AWS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My MicroK8s Cluster Is Now Manged by Azure. What is next?</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure/</guid>
      <description>In a previous blog series MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc - A blog series about my experiences with MicroK8S, WSL, and Azure Arc I had a curiosity to see if I could deploy MicroK8s on my WIndows 10 WSL instance and then manage the WSL instance with Azure Arc and then manage the MicroK8s cluster using Arc-enabled Kubernetes.
So let&amp;rsquo;s refresh here a little. I was able to get a MicroK8s cluster deployed on WSL running on my Windows 10 laptop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc -Part IV - Arc Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-iv-arc-kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 17:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-iv-arc-kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I am going to discuss my experiences with MicroK8S, installing it on Windows Subsystem for Linux, and how to connect the cluster to Azure using Azure Arc-Enabled Kubernetes.
The blog will be broken up into the following three sections:
Installing MicroK8s on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) Azure Arc-enabled servers: Installing Azure Connected Machine Agent Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes: Connecting my MicroK8S cluster to Azure Managing MicroK8s Cluster with Azure Arc-Enabled Kubernetes In this blog I will discuss my experience connecting my newly deploy MicroK8s cluster to Azure using Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc -Part III - Azure Arc</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-iii-azure-arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-iii-azure-arc/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I am going to discuss my experiences with MicroK8S, installing it on Windows Subsystem for Linux, and how to connect the cluster to Azure using Azure Arc-Enabled Kubernetes.
The blog will be broken up into the following three sections:
Installing MicroK8s on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) Azure Arc-enabled servers: Installing Azure Connected Machine Agent Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes: Connecting my MicroK8S cluster to Azure Azure Arc-Enabled Servers - Installing the Azure Connected Machine Agent (Azure Arc Agent) In this blog I will discuss my experience installing the Azure Arc agent, also known as the Azure Connected Machine Agent in in order to manage this WSL instance within Azure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc - Part II - Installing MicroK8S on WSL</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-ii-installing-microk8s-wsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc-part-ii-installing-microk8s-wsl/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I am going to discuss my experiences with MicroK8S, installing it on Windows Subsystem for Linux, and how to connect the cluster to Azure using Azure Arc-Enabled Kubernetes.
The blog will be broken up into the following three sections:
Installing MicroK8s on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) Azure Arc-enabled servers: Installing Azure Connected Machine Agent Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes: Connecting my MicroK8S cluster to Azure Installing MicroK8s on WSL In this blog I will discuss my experience with installing Microk8s on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-wsl-managed-azure-arc/</guid>
      <description>I recently started a new job with a company that isn&amp;rsquo;t a 100% Microsoft shop. It has been many years since I have worked in a environment that everyone wasn&amp;rsquo;t drinking the Microsoft Kool-Aid. Not a bad thing if you do, I did and I loved that flavor. However, new job means new challenges and new way of doing things.
In this blog series I am going to discuss my experiences with MicroK8S.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
