<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Infrastructure as Code on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/infrastructure-as-code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Infrastructure as Code on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/infrastructure-as-code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Odin for Azure Local: A Community Tool Deep Dive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/odin-azure-local-community-tool-deep-dive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/odin-azure-local-community-tool-deep-dive/</guid>
      <description>Section 1: Introduction Key Points to Cover: What is Odin for Azure Local Who built it (Microsoft, hosted on GitHub) The disclaimer: &amp;ldquo;provided as-is, without Microsoft support&amp;rdquo; Why this tool matters for Azure Local practitioners Tool URL: https://azure.github.io/odinforazurelocal/ Current version: 0.12.5 Tone: Honest assessment Not a puff piece—genuine evaluation Useful for practitioners planning deployments Section 2: Tool Overview What Odin Does: Browser-based wizard/decision tree Walks through Azure Local deployment configuration Generates configuration documentation Generates ARM template parameters Includes a Sizer tool Includes Knowledge documentation The 19-Step Workflow: Step Section Purpose 01 Deployment Type Hyperconverged, Multi-Rack, Disconnected, M365 Local 02 Azure Cloud Commercial, Government, China 03 Azure Region Resource registration location 04 Cluster Configuration Standard, Low Capacity, Rack Aware 05 Cluster Size 1-16+ nodes 05.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing AI: A fun test of AI capabilities</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/comparing-ai-fun-test-ai-capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/comparing-ai-fun-test-ai-capabilities/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to My AI Battle Royale! 🥊 Picture this: I&amp;rsquo;m sitting at my desk, drowning in my own scattered thoughts about GitHub Copilot Chat configurations, when I had what can only be described as a &amp;ldquo;brilliant&amp;rdquo; idea. Why not throw my messy brain dump at some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced AI models and see who comes out on top?&#xA;So here we are – welcome to my completely unscientific, totally biased, but hopefully entertaining comparison of AI capabilities!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
