<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infrastructure as Code on This Is My Demo</title><link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/infrastructure-as-code/</link><description>Recent content in Infrastructure as Code on This Is My Demo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/infrastructure-as-code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Odin for Azure Local: A Community Tool Deep Dive</title><link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/odin-azure-local-community-tool-deep-dive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/odin-azure-local-community-tool-deep-dive/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m in the middle of writing The Hyper-V Renaissance—an 18-part series making the case for traditional Hyper-V with Windows Server 2025 as a serious virtualization platform. It&amp;rsquo;s been consuming most of my writing time, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been heads-down on TCO comparisons, cluster builds, and PowerShell automation.
But sometimes you stumble across something that deserves its own post, and you have to step away from the main project for a minute.</description></item><item><title>Comparing AI: A fun test of AI capabilities</title><link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/comparing-ai-fun-test-ai-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/comparing-ai-fun-test-ai-capabilities/</guid><description>Welcome to My AI Battle Royale! 🥊 Picture this: I&amp;rsquo;m sitting at my desk, drowning in my own scattered thoughts about GitHub Copilot Chat configurations, when I had what can only be described as a &amp;ldquo;brilliant&amp;rdquo; idea. Why not throw my messy brain dump at some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most advanced AI models and see who comes out on top?
So here we are – welcome to my completely unscientific, totally biased, but hopefully entertaining comparison of AI capabilities!</description></item></channel></rss>