<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:12:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Entra Permissions Management Podcast</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-19-entra-permissions-management-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-19-entra-permissions-management-podcast/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the privilege to be on The Microsoft 425Show, a Microsoft security chat show. The topic of the podcast was Entra Permissions Management: Partner Perspectives. I had a great time talking with co-workers and with Shannon Kuehn a Senior Product Manager in the Identity product group at Microsoft.
You can access the show podcast from this link Entra Permissions Management: Partner Perspectives or stick around and listen below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Intune&#39;s Proactive Remediation Script Packages to configure clients to retrieve Kerberos tickets for Azure Files.</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-20-using-intunes-proactive-remediation-script-packages-to-configure-clients-to-retrieve-kerberos-tickets-for-azure-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 18:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-20-using-intunes-proactive-remediation-script-packages-to-configure-clients-to-retrieve-kerberos-tickets-for-azure-files/</guid>
      <description>In order to map an Azure File share with Azure AD Kerberos authentication for hybrid user accounts enabled you need to make sure that you configure the clients to retrieve Kerberos tickets.
There are three methods that can accomplish this on your client computers.
Configure an Intune Policy and apply it to the clients. Configure Group Policy on the clients Apply a registry value on the client. I am going to use the registry method, but I will also be using Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Intune Proactive remediation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Festive Tech Calendar 2022</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-20-festive-tech-calendar-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 15:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-20-festive-tech-calendar-2022/</guid>
      <description>This last year I was able to submit a session for the Festive Tech Calender. If you never have heard about the Festive Tech Calendar I suggest you head over to the web site and check out all the different on demand sessions that are available. The Festive Tech Calendar is a community supported and all sessions are created by members of the tech community.
Use Azure Site Recovery to save your bacon&amp;hellip; Christmas ham&amp;hellip; or maybe your job?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating this blog using Hugo and GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/creating-blog-hugo-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 07:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/creating-blog-hugo-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>I am teaching myself as I create this new blog, new technology like Hugo, Front Matter, and Github pages. This post will be updated as I go and become more comfortable with markdown language and everything else that having a static blog in Github requires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/about/</guid>
      <description>What is This Is A Demo? This blog started as a way to play with the idea of moving my old blogs from sources like WordPress, Blogger, etc to something I could control myself. Also something that was free. :) So this blog was born out of the need to learn how to use Hugo, GitHub Pages, and a front end like Front Matter. I have a way to go because everything is all new to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
