<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:12:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Entra Permissions Management Podcast</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-19-entra-permissions-management-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-19-entra-permissions-management-podcast/</guid>
      <description>The Microsoft 425Show I recently had the privilege to be on The Microsoft 425Show, a Microsoft security chat show. The topic of the podcast was Entra Permissions Management: Partner Perspectives. I had a great time talking with co-workers and with Shannon Kuehn a Senior Product Manager in the Identity product group at Microsoft.
You can access the show podcast from this link Entra Permissions Management: Partner Perspectives or stick around and listen below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating this blog using Hugo and GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/creating-blog-hugo-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 07:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/creating-blog-hugo-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>I am teaching myself as I create new blogs new technology like Hugo, Front Matter, and Github pages. This post will be updated as I go and become more familair with markdown language and everything else that having a static blog in Github requires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/about/</guid>
      <description>Our website builds with Hugo static site generator and Mainroad theme. This demo allows you to see what Mainroad based website looks like before deciding to go with it. Just keep in mind that the current demo shows the basics, a small part of what the combination of Hugo and Mainroad can do.
About Mainroad Mainroad is a responsive, simple, clean and content-focused Hugo theme based on the MH Magazine lite WordPress theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
