<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PowerShell on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/powershell/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PowerShell on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:30:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/powershell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure Stack HCI - Part III - Advanced Deployment of A Single Node Cluster</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/azure-stack-hci-part-iii-advanced-deployment-single-node-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/azure-stack-hci-part-iii-advanced-deployment-single-node-cluster/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I plan to blog about everything I know about Azure Stack HCI. So, it should be a very short blog series. Just kidding. Again, I tend to blog about subjects that I am currently working on or will be currently working on. So, Azure Stack HCI is fresh on my mind again these days.
I had planned to have a Part III that would have focused on scaling out a single node cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure Stack HCI - Part II - Deploying A Single Node Cluster</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/azure-stack-hci-part-ii-deploying-single-node-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 17:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/azure-stack-hci-part-ii-deploying-single-node-cluster/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series I plan to blog about everything I know about Azure Stack HCI. So, it should be a very short blog series. Just kidding. Again, I tend to blog about subjects that I am currently working on or will be currently working on. So, Azure Stack HCI is fresh on my mind again these days.
Note: After reading this blog a few times myself I have decided to write another blog but adding more details around areas I did not bring up in this current blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Intune Proactive Remediation Scripts</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/intune-proactive-remediation-scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 14:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/intune-proactive-remediation-scripts/</guid>
      <description>I have been working with Intune Proactive Remediation scripts I wanted to share a few that I am working on.If you want to know more about Intune Proactive Remediation you can check on past blogs of mine.
Using Intune&amp;rsquo;s Proactive Remediation Script Packages to configure clients to retrieve Kerberos tickets for Azure Files.
Intune Proactive Remediation - Check if KB5007253 is installed.
The following scripts are currently in my GitHub repo called ProactiveRemediations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Intune&#39;s Proactive Remediation Script Packages to configure clients to retrieve Kerberos tickets for Azure Files.</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-20-using-intunes-proactive-remediation-script-packages-to-configure-clients-to-retrieve-kerberos-tickets-for-azure-files/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 18:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/2023-01-20-using-intunes-proactive-remediation-script-packages-to-configure-clients-to-retrieve-kerberos-tickets-for-azure-files/</guid>
      <description>In order to map an Azure File share with Azure AD Kerberos authentication for hybrid user accounts enabled you need to make sure that you configure the clients to retrieve Kerberos tickets.
There are three methods that can accomplish this on your client computers.
Configure an Intune Policy and apply it to the clients. Configure Group Policy on the clients Apply a registry value on the client. I am going to use the registry method, but I will also be using Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Intune Proactive remediation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
