<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Arc-Mas on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc-mas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Arc-Mas on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:47:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc-mas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Eight Custom Locations</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-custom-locations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-custom-locations/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 8 - Eight Custom Locations On the eighth day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure carved for me: Eight Custom Locations, sculpting new possibilities for service migrations and innovations.
Day 8: Expanding Horizons with Azure Arc Custom Locations Azure Arc brings us eight maids a-milking, each nurturing the growth of Azure services in the fertile fields of our own environments, no matter how unique or specific they may be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Six Apps Deploying</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-apps-deploying/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 19:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-apps-deploying/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 6 - Six Apps Deploying On the sixth day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure showed to me: Six Apps Deploying, marking innovation at its finest for productivity employing.
Day 6: Fostering Innovation with Azure Arc Azure Arc brings six geese a-laying, each laying the foundation for innovative app deployment, orchestrating the birth of new solutions with cloud-native development across any environment.
Powering Agile Application Development: End-to-End Solutions: From local data collection to cloud-based analytics, Azure Arc provides a comprehensive platform for app development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Four Nodes Connecting</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-nodes-connecting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 19:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-nodes-connecting/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 4 - Four Nodes Connecting On the fourth day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure offered me: Four Nodes Connecting, bringing together a variety of choices for infrastructure selecting.
Day 4: Flexible Infrastructure and Connectivity Azure Arc&amp;rsquo;s fourth gift to us is the power of connection — linking diverse infrastructures from the conventional to the cutting-edge, and ensuring that whether it&amp;rsquo;s Windows Server, Linux, VMware vSphere, or Azure Stack HCI, your nodes are all part of the same, seamlessly managed ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Three Services Scaling</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-services-scaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 19:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-services-scaling/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 3 - Three Services Scaling On the third day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure gifted me: Three Services Scaling, with Azure SQL and PostgreSQL providing no downtime feeling.
Day 3: Data Insights - Azure Arc for Data Services Azure Arc celebrates the season by bringing the robustness of Azure data services directly to Kubernetes clusters, regardless of their location. Imagine Azure SQL Managed Instance and Azure Database for PostgreSQL, not just housed within Azure but anywhere you require – without missing a beat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Two Clusters Flexing</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-clusters-flexing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-clusters-flexing/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 2 - Two Cluster Flexing On the second day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure sent to me: Two Clusters Flexing, managed from Azure, yet running so free.
Embracing Duality: Kubernetes Clusters and Azure Data Services Azure Arc brings duality and harmony between Kubernetes clusters and Azure data services, offering a seamless operational experience that&amp;rsquo;s both managed from Azure and capable of running anywhere.
Azure Arc&amp;rsquo;s Key Messages: Consistent Development and Operations: Azure Arc fosters uniform development and operations of cloud-native applications across any Kubernetes environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure ArcMas - Introduction</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 22:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introducing The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: A Festive Journey Through Cloud Management Happy Holidays, tech enthusiasts! 🎄 As we count down to the end of the year, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to bring you a special gift: &amp;ldquo;The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas.&amp;rdquo; This series is inspired by the classic carol &amp;ldquo;The Twelve Days of Christmas,&amp;rdquo; with a tech twist that celebrates the gifts Azure Arc delivers to IT professionals each day.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
