<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Arc-Mas on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc-mas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Arc-Mas on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc-mas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Two Clusters Flexing</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-clusters-flexing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-clusters-flexing/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 2 - Two Cluster Flexing On the second day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure sent to me: Two Clusters Flexing, managed from Azure, yet running so free.
Embracing Duality: Kubernetes Clusters and Azure Data Services Azure Arc brings duality and harmony between Kubernetes clusters and Azure data services, offering a seamless operational experience that&amp;rsquo;s both managed from Azure and capable of running anywhere.
Azure Arc&amp;rsquo;s Key Messages: Consistent Development and Operations: Azure Arc fosters uniform development and operations of cloud-native applications across any Kubernetes environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure ArcMas - Introduction</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 22:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introducing The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: A Festive Journey Through Cloud Management Happy Holidays, tech enthusiasts! 🎄 As we count down to the end of the year, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to bring you a special gift: &amp;ldquo;The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas.&amp;rdquo; This series is inspired by the classic carol &amp;ldquo;The Twelve Days of Christmas,&amp;rdquo; with a tech twist that celebrates the gifts Azure Arc delivers to IT professionals each day.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
