<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Arc on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/categories/azure-arc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Arc on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/categories/azure-arc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas - Two Clusters Flexing</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-clusters-flexing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas-clusters-flexing/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 2 - Two Cluster Flexing On the second day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure sent to me: Two Clusters Flexing, managed from Azure, yet running so free.
Embracing Duality: Kubernetes Clusters and Azure Data Services Azure Arc brings duality and harmony between Kubernetes clusters and Azure data services, offering a seamless operational experience that&amp;rsquo;s both managed from Azure and capable of running anywhere.
Azure Arc&amp;rsquo;s Key Messages: Consistent Development and Operations: Azure Arc fosters uniform development and operations of cloud-native applications across any Kubernetes environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure ArcMas - A Console In A Cloud Tree</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-console-cloud-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 22:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-console-cloud-tree/</guid>
      <description>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: Day 1 - Centralized Management On the first day of Azure Arc-Mas, Azure granted me: A Console in a Cloud Tree.
Single Control Plane Across Environments Azure Arc is like the partridge in a pear tree at the heart of your environment&amp;rsquo;s management, extending the familiar Azure services to wherever your resources reside. It simplifies the complex, multi-faceted nature of modern IT landscapes by offering a unified management experience, enabling you to view and manage your resources irrespective of their physical or cloud location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure ArcMas - Introduction</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 22:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arcmas-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introducing The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas: A Festive Journey Through Cloud Management Happy Holidays, tech enthusiasts! 🎄 As we count down to the end of the year, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to bring you a special gift: &amp;ldquo;The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas.&amp;rdquo; This series is inspired by the classic carol &amp;ldquo;The Twelve Days of Christmas,&amp;rdquo; with a tech twist that celebrates the gifts Azure Arc delivers to IT professionals each day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas!</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas/</guid>
      <description>For those that are not aware there is a very awesome resource provided by the Cloud Family called the Festive Tech Calendar. The Festive Tech Calendar is a free, month-long, fun tech event that takes place throughout December. The event features new content from different communities and people around the globe. The event is organized by Cloud Family and is aimed at people from all communities who want to participate in a fun and engaging session that is a bit different from a normal conference.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
