<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes on This Is My Demo</title>
    <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc-enabled-kubernetes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Azure Arc-enabled Kubernetes on This Is My Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:18:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/azure-arc-enabled-kubernetes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 12 Days of Azure Arc-Mas!</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/12-days-azure-arc-mas/</guid>
      <description>For those that are not aware there is a very awesome resource provided by the Cloud Family called the Festive Tech Calendar. The Festive Tech Calendar is a free, month-long, fun tech event that takes place throughout December. The event features new content from different communities and people around the globe. The event is organized by Cloud Family and is aimed at people from all communities who want to participate in a fun and engaging session that is a bit different from a normal conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My MicroK8s Cluster Is Now Manged by Azure. What is next? - Part II - Monitoring</title>
      <link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure-part-ii-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 20:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/microk8s-cluster-manged-azure-part-ii-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>This is next blog in a series of blogs I just started that share my experiences with integrating Azure services with my on-premises deployment of MicroK8s Kubernetes cluster running in WSL. These blog series are an extension of another blog series I did called MicroK8S and WSL Managed by Azure Arc.
At a high level there is a lot of Azure Services we can integrate and use with our Kubernetes clusters running anywhere, such as on-premises, or even GCP and AWS.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
