<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Windows Server 2025 on This Is My Demo</title><link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/windows-server-2025/</link><description>Recent content in Windows Server 2025 on This Is My Demo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:19:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://thisismydemo.cloud/tags/windows-server-2025/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Welcome to the Hyper-V Renaissance</title><link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/hyper-renaissance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 05:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/hyper-renaissance/</guid><description>Introduction A Perfect Storm Creates Opportunity If you&amp;rsquo;ve been watching the virtualization market over the past eighteen months, you&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed something extraordinary: a once-stable industry thrown into chaos by a single acquisition. When Broadcom completed its $69 billion purchase of VMware in November 2023, few anticipated how dramatically—and rapidly—the landscape would shift. What followed wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a pricing adjustment; it was a fundamental restructuring that has sent shockwaves through data centers worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the Cloud: 2025 Virtualization Licensing Guide - Part II</title><link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/choosing-your-virtualization-platform-2025-licensing-analysis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:02:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/choosing-your-virtualization-platform-2025-licensing-analysis/</guid><description>Welcome to Part 2 of our &amp;ldquo;Beyond the Cloud: The Case for On-Premises Virtualization&amp;rdquo; series. In our introductory post, we explored why organizations are reconsidering their virtualization strategies post-VMware acquisition. In Part 1, we conducted a detailed five-year Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) analysis comparing Windows Hyper-V, Azure VMware Solution (AVS), and Azure Local, revealing how different cost structures impact long-term budgets.
A key factor driving those cost differences was how each platform&amp;rsquo;s licensing model works.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the Cloud: Rethinking Virtualization Post-VMware</title><link>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/rethinking-virtualization-post-vmware/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 19:36:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://thisismydemo.cloud/post/rethinking-virtualization-post-vmware/</guid><description>From My Perspective as a Microsoft Azure Hybrid MVP – Two Decades in Microsoft Hybrid &amp;amp; HCI I write this blog as a longtime Microsoft advocate with two decades of hands-on experience—from early Hyper-V in 2008 to today&amp;rsquo;s Azure Local. This series aims to highlight the potential of Windows Server Failover Clustering (WSFC) as a viable alternative for organizations transitioning away from VMware, especially in light of Broadcom&amp;rsquo;s acquisition. While I value Azure&amp;rsquo;s Cloud and Hybrid offerings, I believe Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s current messaging overlooks WSFC&amp;rsquo;s capabilities in providing cost-effective, high-availability solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>